<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kumar Abhishek</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kumar Abhishek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Kumar Abhishek</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Search Engine</title>
      <link>/project/HouseImageSearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/HouseImageSearch/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;developing-a-platform-for-automatic-real-estate-image-tagging-and-keyword-based-search:151adb2c1b0b500fde9d0ebeb5a4b705&#34;&gt;Developing a platform for automatic real estate image tagging and keyword based search&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal is to build a platform for potential real estate sellers to upload their property images and have them tagged automatically (with no or very little manual effort) according to the scene attributes such as room type, architecture, styling, etc. These generated tags can then be utilized to develop an efficient keyword based search of real estate properties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multiple feature engineering techniques are used to train a robust house image classifier. Different CNN architectures are used along with multiple open source and proprietary image datasets to enhance the classification accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;tools-used-python-opencv-keras-aws:151adb2c1b0b500fde9d0ebeb5a4b705&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tools used&lt;/strong&gt;: Python, OpenCV, Keras, AWS&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extraction from Scanned Document Images</title>
      <link>/project/Extraction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/Extraction/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-science-team-altisource:e0dfae3cea95b4cb532f9aa9d0cfb9ec&#34;&gt;Data Science Team, Altisource&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project involved developing a tool for the automated extraction and parsing of various fields present in scanned mortgage document images. The software was able to handle multiple pre-defined document types with variations in the number of fields per page and was also invariant to image skew and noise. Complex heuristics based approaches, image processing, and NLP techniques were used to make the tool robust to such variations, and extract appropriate field values from the documents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;tools-used-python-imagemagick-tesseract-ocr-opencv:e0dfae3cea95b4cb532f9aa9d0cfb9ec&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tools used&lt;/strong&gt;: Python, ImageMagick, Tesseract OCR, OpenCV&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Processing and Visualizations</title>
      <link>/project/DocClassification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/DocClassification/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-science-team-altisource:943d9bcebf6280690ec291a80f86b61e&#34;&gt;Data Science Team, Altisource&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;!-- ### Summarization and Visualization of Large Volumes of Broadcast Video Data
#### **Guide**: Dr. Prithwijit Guha, Assistant Professor, Department of Electronics &amp; Electrical Engineering, IIT Guwahati --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of this project was to develop a classification pipeline for the categorization scanned mortgage documents for loan underwriting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;tools-used-python-r-c:943d9bcebf6280690ec291a80f86b61e&#34;&gt;Tools used: Python, R, C++&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proof of Concepts (PoCs) using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/project/DPE/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/DPE/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-platform-engineering-dpe-team-wipro-analytics-wipro-ltd:abf9351ea2183cfdff7861aa26c7ad84&#34;&gt;Data Platform Engineering  (DPE) Team, Wipro Analytics, Wipro Ltd.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;!-- #### **Guide**: Dr. Prithwijit Guha, Assistant Professor, Department of Electronics &amp; Electrical Engineering, IIT Guwahati --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I worked with the DPE team on a number of PoCs for various potential clients using machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I developed a utility for monitoring and predicting AWS EC2 instances’ usage levels with AWS CloudWatch to recommend downsizing and reserving of the instances to save on the billing costs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I worked on analyzing and predicting the failures in a Hadoop multi-node cluster using machine learning models for a USA based
software and hardware giant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I developed an automated ticket handling system for a USA based hardware and software giant using machine learning models
on the Microsoft Azure Platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;tools-used-jupyter-notebook-python-r-hadoop-aws-microsoft-azure-numenta-nupic:abf9351ea2183cfdff7861aa26c7ad84&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tools used&lt;/strong&gt;: Jupyter Notebook, Python, R, Hadoop, AWS, Microsoft Azure, Numenta Nupic&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Processing and Visualizations</title>
      <link>/project/AMG/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/AMG/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;application-management-group-wipro-ltd:4788cf420e719667200a3155e8450a99&#34;&gt;Application Management Group, Wipro Ltd.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;!-- #### **Guide**: Dr. Prithwijit Guha, Assistant Professor, Department of Electronics &amp; Electrical Engineering, IIT Guwahati --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I worked with the Application Management Group for a short time where I build tools for monitoring the operating system version and other software components (Microsoft Office, McAfee Agent, etc.) of all of Wipro’s assets (more than 180,000 laptops, desktops, servers, etc.) for compliance tracking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;tools-used-apache-hive-apache-sqoop-microsoft-sql-server-d3-hierarchical-pie-python:4788cf420e719667200a3155e8450a99&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tools used&lt;/strong&gt;: Apache Hive, Apache Sqoop, Microsoft SQL Server, d3-hierarchical-pie, Python&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Minutiae Count Based Method for Fake Fingerprint Detection</title>
      <link>/publication/fake-fingerprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/fake-fingerprint/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/files/VisionNet15.pdf&#34;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt; to local copy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Detection in Big Data</title>
      <link>/project/Apollo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/Apollo/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;apollo-platforms-group-now-wipro-holmes-wipro-ltd:53ef6cbd4a0cc72f928711bb7fe6361e&#34;&gt;Apollo Platforms Group (now Wipro HOLMES), Wipro Ltd.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;!-- #### **Guide**: Dr. Prithwijit Guha, Assistant Professor, Department of Electronics &amp; Electrical Engineering, IIT Guwahati --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I joined Wipro’s Fraud Detection and Prevention and Anomaly Detection team, Apollo, as a part of the STAR batch, the fast track leadership development program consisting of engineering graduates from premier colleges of India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was responsible for the implementation and the execution of fraud detection rules which were run on the employee data to discover the potential anomalies for a wide variety of use cases, followed by building predictive models for fraud detection. The rules were executed on a single node Hadoop cluster (AWS EC2 instance) with the data being stored on AWS S3 and handled by Hive and MySQL.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was involved in Apollo’s pilot for 3 potential clients, and responsible for the rule execution (on Hive), result
validation and the final anomaly report generation (using JasperSoft).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;tools-used-apache-hive-mysql-aws-ec2-aws-s3-jaspersoft:53ef6cbd4a0cc72f928711bb7fe6361e&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tools used&lt;/strong&gt;: Apache Hive, MySQL, AWS EC2, AWS S3, JasperSoft&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast Video Analytics</title>
      <link>/project/BTP/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/BTP/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;summarization-and-visualization-of-large-volumes-of-broadcast-video-data:e378a736598b64f3dedfff792ea07a92&#34;&gt;Summarization and Visualization of Large Volumes of Broadcast Video Data&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;guide-dr-prithwijit-guha-assistant-professor-department-of-electronics-electrical-engineering-iit-guwahati:e378a736598b64f3dedfff792ea07a92&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guide&lt;/strong&gt;: Dr. Prithwijit Guha, Assistant Professor, Department of Electronics &amp;amp; Electrical Engineering, IIT Guwahati&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective of this project was to detect the presentation format of broadcast news videos. Although there has been previous work done on the classification of the various elements present on a frame from a news video, all of this work&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[To be updated]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;tools-used-c-python-opencv-gnu-scientific-library-gsl-libsvm-openshot-video-editor:e378a736598b64f3dedfff792ea07a92&#34;&gt;Tools used: C++, Python, OpenCV, GNU Scientific Library (GSL), LibSVM, OpenShot Video Editor&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Fake Fingerprints</title>
      <link>/project/biometrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/biometrics/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;detection-of-fake-fingerprints-using-minutiae-count:7a32332d0d7e122343d9fb03f98ed2c9&#34;&gt;Detection of Fake Fingerprints using Minutiae Count&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;guides-dr-m-k-bhuyan-associate-professor-department-of-electronics-electrical-engineering-iit-guwahati:7a32332d0d7e122343d9fb03f98ed2c9&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guides&lt;/strong&gt;: Dr. M K Bhuyan, Associate Professor, Department of Electronics &amp;amp; Electrical Engineering, IIT Guwahati&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We proposed an algorithm based on the minutiae count for detecting the fake fingerprints generated using, but not limited to gelatin, Play-Doh and Silicone molds. On testing the algorithm on the FVC (Fingerprint Verification Competition) datasets, available from BioLab, University of Bologna, Italy, the algorithm achieved an accuracy of over 85%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The results of the project have been &lt;a href=&#34;/publication/fake-fingerprint&#34;&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in the Elsevier ScienceDirect Procedia Computer Science.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- ![Image of the result obtained on the test kit](/img/uploads/TestKit_Image.jpg) ![Image of the result obtained on the test kit](/img/uploads/TestKit_ROI.jpg) --&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;tools-used-matlab:7a32332d0d7e122343d9fb03f98ed2c9&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tools used&lt;/strong&gt;: MATLAB&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Invasive Measurement of Heart Rate and Hemoglobin Concentration through Fingertip</title>
      <link>/publication/non-invasive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/non-invasive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/files/SPICES2015.pdf&#34;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt; to local copy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An algorithm for optical character recognition of the embossed digits on credit cards</title>
      <link>/project/IWIn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/IWIn/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;guides:1686baaa22dc87363d243aee0f66c051&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guides&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mr. Raghavendra Hosabettu, Senior Consultant, Chief Technical Office, Wipro Technologies, Bangalore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mr. Anil Kumar Lenka, Senior Consultant, Chief Technical Office, Wipro Technologies, Bangalore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main motivation of this project was to make online payment easy and hassle free for the consumers, by developing something that assists them in online  transactions, while still maintaining their privacy. Present day payment techniques involve swipe or manually entering the card number. We plan to change this approach by allowing the user to take an image of the card using the mobile application (app), thus eliminating the need for any hardware as well as the hassle of manually entering the digits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The end goal of this project was to develop a elegant solution for online transactions for the end users, without the need of any additional hardware. This app was intended to help the end users during online payments, wherein, instead of entering the 15 or 16 digits of their card number, they can simply take an image of the card and the application will, in turn, extract the digits from the image acquired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-proposed-algorithm-was-able-to-detect-the-digits-with-an-accuracy-of-83-with-experiments-carried-out-on-cards-issued-by-different-corporations-such-as-visa-mastercard-maestro-american-express-and-rupay:1686baaa22dc87363d243aee0f66c051&#34;&gt;The proposed algorithm was able to detect the digits with an accuracy of 83%, with experiments carried out on cards issued by different corporations such as VISA, MasterCard, Maestro, American Express and RuPay.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/uploads/CardImage.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/uploads/Card_ROI.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/uploads/Card_ROI_1.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/uploads/Card_ROI_2.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/uploads/Card_ROI_BW.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/uploads/Card_SegmentedDigits.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;tools-used-c-python-opencv-matlab-roborealm:1686baaa22dc87363d243aee0f66c051&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tools used&lt;/strong&gt;: C++, Python, OpenCV, MATLAB, RoboRealm&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-invasive measurement of blood parameters through fingertip</title>
      <link>/project/design-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/design-project/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;summarization-and-visualization-of-large-volumes-of-broadcast-video-data:35aad3244ad8893b8e7b0c4b490af3a3&#34;&gt;Summarization and Visualization of Large Volumes of Broadcast Video Data&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;guide-dr-ramesh-kumar-sonkar-assistant-professor-department-of-electronics-electrical-engineering-iit-guwahati:35aad3244ad8893b8e7b0c4b490af3a3&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guide&lt;/strong&gt;: Dr. Ramesh Kumar Sonkar, Assistant Professor, Department of Electronics &amp;amp; Electrical Engineering, IIT Guwahati&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objective was to estimate blood parameters using Photo Plethysmo Graphy (PPG). PPG is a simple, low cost reliable optical technique that can be used to detect blood parameters by passing Electromagnetic Light rays through the skin. The information about blood parameters is obtained non-invasively in contrast to the painful and inconvenient invasive methods, with measurements generally made at the skin surface whereupon it is easy to record data. During the process, change in volume caused by blood pressure pulse is detected by illuminating the skin from a light emitting diode (LED) and measuring the amount of light either transmitted or reflected through a light detector. In the proposed analysis, we plan to collect PPG signal via fingertip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An IR transmitting LED is used to illuminate the subject’s fingertip. The variation in collector current for photo-transistor depends on change in blood volume beneath the skin during signal acquisition. Signal recorded is filtered from high frequency noise and unwanted DC component. Output of the signal conditioning circuit is fed to a computer software as input to calculate the heart rate and the hemoglobin concentration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The results of the project have been &lt;a href=&#34;/publication/non-invasive&#34;&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in the IEEE International Conference on Signal Processing, Informatics, Communication and Energy Systems (SPICES) 2015, Kozhikode, India, February 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/uploads/PPG_MATLAB.png&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The unfiltered signal, as collected from the circuit&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/uploads/PPG_Oscilloscope.png&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Filtered signal as observed on the Digital Oscilloscope&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;tools-used-matlab-arduino-ni-multisim:35aad3244ad8893b8e7b0c4b490af3a3&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tools used&lt;/strong&gt;: MATLAB, Arduino, NI MultiSim&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Enhanced Algorithm for the Quantification of Human Chorionic Gonadotropin (hCG) Level in Commercially Available Home Pregnancy Test Kits</title>
      <link>/publication/pregnancy-test-kits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/pregnancy-test-kits/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/files/NCC2014.pdf&#34;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt; to local copy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorimetric Analysis with a Mobile Phone</title>
      <link>/project/IITH/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/IITH/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;an-enhanced-algorithm-for-the-quantification-of-human-chorionic-gonadotropin-hcg-level-in-commercial-home-pregnancy-test-kits:92fd04e27706fcb34d0de294af8e9e06&#34;&gt;An enhanced algorithm for the quantification of human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG) level in commercial home pregnancy test kits&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;guides:92fd04e27706fcb34d0de294af8e9e06&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guides&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dr. Sumohana Channappayya, Associate Professor, Department of Electrical Engineering, IIT Hyderabad&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dr. Dhananjaya Dendukuri, Co-founder &amp;amp; CEO, Achira Labs Pvt. Ltd., Bangalore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a continuation and an improvement of the work &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;An Automated Algorithm for the Quantification of hCG Level in Novel Fabric-based Home Pregnancy Test Kits&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;, by K Manasa et al. accepted for presentation at IEEE Asilomar Conference on Signals, Systems and Computers 2013, Pacific Grove, CA USA, November 2013.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The overall aim of the project was to develop a novel image processing algorithm that can be used in conjunction with pregnancy kits based on lateral flow immunoassay techniques for the automated detection and classification of human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG). At present, home pregnancy kits give only qualitative information about the presence of hCG in urinary/serum samples. An analysis of the test kit’s output image using the proposed algorithm will lead to quantitative information about the concentration of hCG, which is in fact more helpful for medical purposes than just a binary yes/no result to the pregnancy test. The algortihm first segmented the image to locate the stripes and then identified the control and test stripes. The color components of the test stripes were then classified into different levels based on the intensities of the test stripes. Furthermore, the algorithm was implemented on a mobile platform which is of great value addition in case of remote rural health monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-proposed-algorithm-produced-results-with-accuracy-consistently-above-95-which-was-a-considerable-improvement-over-the-previously-achieved-80:92fd04e27706fcb34d0de294af8e9e06&#34;&gt;The proposed algorithm produced results with accuracy consistently above 95%, which was a considerable improvement over the previously achieved 80%.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The results of the project have been &lt;a href=&#34;/publication/pregnancy-test-kits&#34;&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in the IEEE National Conference on Communications (NCC) 2014, Kanpur, India, February 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- ![Image of the result obtained on the test kit](/img/uploads/TestKit_Image.jpg) ![Image of the result obtained on the test kit](/img/uploads/TestKit_ROI.jpg) --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/uploads/TestKit_Image.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Image of the result obtained on the test kit&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/uploads/TestKit_ROI.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;In the entire image of the test kit, the only region which concerns us is the small window where the test results appear. Therefore, we crop that particular region and use it for further processing. As it is evident from the image, the stripe on the left side is known as Test Stripe and that on the right is known as the Control Stripe.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;tools-used-matlab:92fd04e27706fcb34d0de294af8e9e06&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tools used&lt;/strong&gt;: MATLAB&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
